So, now, let's talk about the different options we have for base foundation models.
So, we have to choose based on a lot of different factors.
In the end, it's going to come down to the model types, the performance requirements you have,
the capabilities of the model, the constraints you have, the compliance you need and so on.
Also, some models may provide you different levels of customization.
Some models may be smaller, others bigger.
There could be different levels for inference, so how to basically get an output of the model.
You may have different licensing agreements.
You may have different requirements on context windows.
So, how big you can send the, how much data you can send it to a foundation model,
as well as latency.
So, how fast the model will come back to you with an answer.
You may also have different factors such as, is a model, is a model, a multi model,
which means that it can take a wide combination of types of inputs.
For example, audio, text and video together, and also give you very types of outputs.
For example, again, images, audio, video, text, about altogether at the same time.
So, it's, there's no clear answer, of course, it's a free to test.
But there is something called Amazon Titan, and because this is an AWS certification,
we're studying for, I believe, Amazon Titan is going to appear at the exam.
So, what is Amazon Titan?
Well, it is the high performing foundation model directly from AWS.
So, you have different levels of Amazon Titan.
But it can do images, texts, and you also have multimodal choices,
all via the same API you have on Amazon Bedrock.
As well, it can be customized with your own data.
So, you can fine tune Amazon Titan, and that can be very handy.
Also, for example, to make a decision on the model,
usually the smaller models are going to be more cost-effective,
but they usually know less things.
So, it's a bunch of balancing acts really based on what your business needs is on.
So, let's have a look at four models to see if we can understand a little bit how our
process will go into.
So, we have Amazon Titan, and we're going to compare Amazon Titan text express.
We have, I'll call it Lama, but maybe Lama, Lama too,
which is some model out of meta.
We have cloud, out of from entropy.
And then we have stability AI, which created something called stable diffusion.
So, first of all, the last model is for image generation only.
So, if you want to just image, maybe the last model we can build for you,
but for the other ones, you have different kinds of capabilities.
So, if we look at features, for example,
well, Amazon Titan can do texts, and it can do it in 100 plus languages.
Lama too can do large-scale tasks, dialogue, and in English.
And cloud can have also text generation, and also multi language.
So, it comes down to testing how the model reacts to your inputs.
And one thing that may be very important is the number of tokens you can have
as an input to the model.
So, Amazon, we have 8k tokens.
Lama too, we have 4k tokens, and cloud, we have 200k tokens.
So, that means that on cloud, you can send a lot more words
into your context windows.
And so, cloud will have more memory and will be able to
intake bigger inputs, which may be very important, for example.
You may want to send a big context window when you're dealing with a big code base,
or when you have to read an entire book, and ask questions about that book,
then maybe cloud is going to be a better fit.
So, the use cases really depends on the models, but to be fair,
all these models start to look the same and have the same kind of capabilities.
They're all converging towards the same thing.
So, it's down to many, many testing.
But so, Amazon Titan is going to be around content creation, classification,
and education.
Lama too is going to be around text generation and customer service.
Cloud could be for analysis, for casting, and document comparison.
This is mainly due to the fact it has a higher number of token as an inputs.
And stability AI is going to be for image creation, for advertising,
media, and so on.
And so pricing can be a big factor again.
So, here the pricing is given for 1,000 tokens given to the model.
So, as you can see, Amazon Titan text express is very cheap.
It's much cheaper than Lama too, and Lama too is much cheaper than cloud.
So, again, this could be a big one because obviously,
the more expensive models may give you better answers.
But sometimes, the less expensive models can still give you good answers,
but they're going to be a lot more cost effective.
And as well, for stability AI, based on the image you generate,
it may cost you as well some money.
So, be conscious because you can very, very quickly accumulate a lot of costs with AI.
So, I hope you liked it, and I will see you in the next lecture.